digitalmediaglobe.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy 1 - Digital Media Globe

This **Privacy Policy** governs the manner in which **DigitalMediaGlobe** collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the[ **http://DigitalMediaGlobe.com**](http://digitalmediaglobe.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by **DigitalMediaGlobe.**

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visit to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

###  **Personal identification information**

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

###  **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.

###  **User Comments**

 **DigitalMediaGlobe** allows users to comment on the site. However, we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on **DigitalMediaGlobe** please refrain from using content that is not suitable. Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to **DigitalMediaGlobe** and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through **DigitalMediaGlobe** have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.  Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

###  **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. The user’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for recordkeeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

###  **How we use collected information**

 **DigitalMediaGlobe.com** collects and uses the user’s personal information for the following purposes:

  *  ** _To personalize the user experience:_** We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  *  ** _To improve our Site:_** We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  *  ** _To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature:_** To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  *  ** _To send periodic emails:_** The E-mail address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

###  **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

###  **Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes, provided that you have given us your permission.

###  **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

###  **Advertising**

The ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###  **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy at[ **http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) **.  **

###  **Changes to this privacy policy**

DigitalMediaGlobe.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

###  **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, Visit our [Contact Page](http://digitalmediaglobe.com/contact-us-now/ "Contact Us Now") or please contact us at [info@DigitalMediaGlobe.com](mailto:info@DigitalMediaGlobe.com)
